[{"answer": "I think -- I mean, I hate to try to analyze events without just knowing -- without just reporting complete facts, but my impression is that these protesters, these pro-Mubarak protesters were allowed to get close to the square perhaps in the hopes that they would push out the anti-Mubarak protesters, that they would end this once and for all.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you think that Mubarak and his government officials realize that the full force against the media and protesters backfired on them in terms of PR around the world?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Certainly it is a problem.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "How much of a problem is that going to be, do you think?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, as you know, Egypt is dependent on imports of foodstuffs from abroad.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What is the situation in relation to those kind of imports?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think, you know, the president, and the vice president, and the prime ministers have gone as far as possible to respond to the demands of these young people.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I would apologize to any journalist or any foreigner or any Egyptian for that matter that has been subjected to this harsh treatment.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Would you like to take this opportunity to apologize?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "His demeanor was well.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "What was his demeanor like?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, two issues here.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "If he was to suddenly leave it could actually provoke more chaos than if he stays for the transition?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it certainly has been really appalling what's happened.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like that in terms of a concerted effort by a government to gag the media in such brutal way?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I'm fine, thank you.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "So far the protests in Tahrir have been very peaceful.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "How has the day been for you out there?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "I don't think he's going now.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Is he going to go now, do you think?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Do you think they still want Mubarak gone now?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I'm not sure he really does feel optimistic.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Wolf, is he right to feel optimistic?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "It's a very difficult foreign policy decision.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Is this one of the most difficult foreign policy decisions you have seen an American president have for quite some time?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, I think John's comments were correct.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "How worried are you about Israel which is seeing its number one protector in many ways now being exposed to the will of the people and that could go anywhere?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I think we have to recognize and accept that it will be the people of Egypt that will ultimately determine the course of Egypt, including its leadership.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Clearly a peaceful, relatively well-organized transition is the preferred option for everybody because it's less chaotic, but if the protests continue, they get bigger, they get angrier and there is more violence, isn't Mubarak just going to have to go?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I think it's clear he's going to leave no later than September, but my sense is he will probably leave before then although I don't think he will want to appear to be chased out of office.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Michael Chertoff, When will leave?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "First, let me say I think it's a wonderful thing to see democracy in action and people going into the streets not to be violent but to demonstrate peacefully.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "As somebody who has been a leading light in Homeland Security, what do you see now as the threat to America's security by what you are seeing in Egypt?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, right now the army appears to be playing the role of a stabilizing force.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What would be the worst that could happen from America's point of view?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "We are worrying about our own country.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "ORGAN: Mr. Prime Minister, can I ask you, have you been surprised by the events in Egypt, and do you believe that President Mubarak should now go immediately?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I haven't really thought about it.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Do you believe that this is a crisis for the whole of the Middle East?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "First of all, I would like to thank the American people that have always helped Tunisia since our independence.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "How can they help you in Tunisia?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "We have already entered negotiations, and a commission has been formed to revise the laws to make this election free and transparent, an election that will allow all parties to participate with the same chances.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "And do you believe that you're going to find successful peace and prosperity in your country in the next few years?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, we've again experienced some remarkable changes, Piers.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What is your take on what's going on right now?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "We just heard the prime minister of Tunisia talking about the power of Facebook and Twitter in particular on the revolution there.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Mobile phones are working, and the Internet did come back on several days ago.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Are mobile phones working?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "No way, absolutely not.", "docId": "110204pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Is it possible to make any kind of prediction with any certainty?", "qSentId": 454}]